### Aidan Glickman

contact@aidanglickman.com

aidanglickman.com

#### github.com/AidanGlickman

Software engineer with experience in machine learning, computer vision, biotech and full stack development. Effective leader and project manager who is a self starter and values team collaboration. Problem solver who builds novel, effective solutions. Eager learner who is excited about new technologies, paradigms and methods.

# Work Experience

Full Stack Engineer

Autofleet

September 2020 - October 2020

Tel Aviv, Israel

A smart mobility startup focused on Vehicle-as-a-Service solutions and ML driven insights

- Contributed to front and backend for pooled vehicle rerouting and route matching
- Conceptualized and rewrote integration with Tesla
- Communicated to coworkers in Hebrew

ML & Engineering Intern
OWAL

August 2019 - May 2020

Brooklyn, NY

A computer vision startup focused on surveillance and security

- Built a set of detectors to ensure client cameras are working properly
- Engineered front end to display data and analytics on camera statistics
- Collaborate directly with CTO to identify and implement novel solutions for engineering problems

Summer Intern

June 2018 - August 2018, July 2019 - August 2019

Immunobrain Checkpoint

Rehovot, Israel

An early stage biopharmaceutical company developing treatments for neurological disorders

- Developed image processing pipeline to automate research tasks
- Performed lab and microscopy work for research on macular degeneration
- Worked and communicated with co-workers in Hebrew

Investment Intern

8VC

July 2017 - August 2017

San Francisco, California

A venture capital firm aimed at leading technological advancement in existing industries

- Conducted due diligence on research laboratories and the technologies they were pursuing
- Contributed data and background information for slide deck on Bio-IT
- Attended pitch meetings and compiled summaries of startup pitches and internal company discussions

Tech Consulting & Misc.

September 2016 - present

Self Employed (Firerock Technologies LLC)

- Freelance tech consulting and other work, including building software, tech-stack migration services, etc.
- Hardware and other technology component sales on online auction platforms (gross sales of \$40,000 to date)
- Build custom business and gaming PCs for clients
- Design and sell original artwork on global online marketplace for print on demand products

# Main Technologies

Python

numPy, SciKit, OpenCV, Many other libraries

JavaScript

NodeJS, Express, VueJS, ES11, Many other libraries/frameworks

Deployment

Docker, Kubernetes, TravisCI/CircleCI

Functional Programming

Scheme (Racket), Lambda Calculus

Low Level

C, x86 & 6502 Assembly

Linux Skills

Shell scripting, Comfortable in shell

Other Languages

Java, Octave/Matlab, Ability to learn very quickly

## Education

Bergen County Academies Academy for Technology and Computer Science

3.85/4.0 unweighted GPA

4.0/4.0 CS GPA

36/36 ACT

5/5 AP Computer Science A, Calculus AB & BC, Statistics, US Government

#### CS Coursework

Machine Learning

Linear Algebra & Differential

Numerical Models & Simulations

2016-2020

Hackensack, NJ

Equations

Artificial Intelligence C & Data Structures Advanced Topics in CS AP Computer Science A

Cybersecurity
Internet of Things

# Extracurricular Activities

President

September 2017 - September 2019

BCA Cybersecurity Club

- Present and teach cybersecurity concepts to fellow students at weekly sessions
- Compete in CTFs (Capture the Flag cybersecurity competitions)
- Launched and coordinated BCACTF, a beginner-focused cybersecurity competition
- Captained Air Force Association CyberPatriot team to 3rd in New Jersey, 80th in nation in our first year

Director

November 2018 - February 2020

hackBCA

- Organize and run hackathons (hackBCA V) and other educational events for the country's longest running high school hackathon
- Run board of directors overseeing various aspects of event planning including guest speakers, event logistics, onsite technology, and sponsorships
- Direct weeklong summer program for rising high school freshmen to introduce them to computer science

Webmaster & Peer Tutor

October 2018 - June 2020

BCA NHS Chapter

- Elected to board of school's NHS chapter
- Fulfilled campaign promise to build bca-nhs.org web platform
- Tutor fellow students in CS and math